kseibi.com 2011-12-31

# KSEIBI Privacy Center

©2011 KSEIBI. All Rights Reserved.

**What information does KSEIBI collect and how does KSEIBI use this information?**

\--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

**During your visit to our web-site, you are under no obligation to provide any personal information to KSEIBI.**

  * We may request personal information from you which may include your name, address, e-mail KSEIBI to communicate and market our products to our customers, to understand customer buying behavior, and to conduct product research.

  * We may conduct promotional sweepstakes or other contests on our web-site, which require certain personal information for participation in the promotion or contest. This information is used to contact the winners and for other marketing purposes.

  * In an effort to continually improve our products and services, we will periodically contact our customers in order to conduct KSEIBI market research and on-line surveys. This may involve KSEIBI. 

  * KSEIBI.com may run "opt-in" e-mail campaigns and newsletters. Information that you have provided in your registration and information given through participation in on-line promotions may be used by KSEIBI.com to further customize the content of the e-mail promotions that you have "opt-ed in" to receive.

  * Our web servers may automatically monitor the number of visitors, the average time spent on the site, the popularity of our web-sites, and any programming errors or failures on any of our web-sites in order to determine the effectiveness of the KSEIBI web-sites.

Does KSEIBI share your information with other third parties?

\--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

  * We do not sell, rent, or trade your specific personal information to third parties.
  * KSEIBI will not share your e-mail address or personal information with any other parties without your prior consent; however, we may share personal information with our business partners in order to service, repair, or fulfill your KSEIBI products. 

  * KSEIBI may share aggregate data about our sales, customers, traffic patterns, and other related site information with respectable third parties. None of this data is related to any individual's name without their consent. 

**What is the policy regarding KSEIBI's ownership of information?**

\-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

  * If you feel that we have not substantially maintained the above policy or if you have any concerns about our policy, please contact [KSEIBI.com webmaster](mailto:webmaster@kseibi.com) and we will promptly evaluate the situation. 

\--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

What about KSEIBI's links to other sites?

  * We may add external links to other related web-sites that we believe are consistent with the KSEIBI brand and our customer interests. We certainly try to link to web-sites that maintain the same high regard for privacy on the Internet as we do; however, we are not responsible for the content that may be on such linked sites. Additionally, the existence of any external link does not suggest that KSEIBI endorses the linked company, product or service. 

\--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

How do I contact KSEIBI regarding this policy statement?

  * Your opinions and ideas are important to the success and improvement at KSEIBI. Should you choose to submit an opinion, idea, or suggestion through our web-sites, you agree to allow KSEIBI to use that feedback without restriction and free of charge. In instances such as online product research, you may be asked to agree to terms of a KSEIBI prepared consent form related to the provision of such information.
